fbunseen.com 2017-12-29

# Privacy | FB unseen

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, products and services, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To personalize your experience

(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 

• To improve our service (we continually strive to improve our service offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

• To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our service. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our service and not to information collected offline.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our services privacy policy. 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. info@fbunseen.com
